# RAGHU MANDALOJI (1) Featured

Java Developer seeking roles in Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Development, Project Management, Change Management, Requirement Gathering, Agile Methodology, Spring Boot, Apache Tomcat, Hibernate, Eclipse, HTML, CSS, Javascript, core java.



Current Designation: Java Developer Total Experience: 2 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Current Company: Bracket Technology Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Hyderabad / Secunderabad Highest Degree:

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Hyderabad

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: Java/Software Developer, Software Engineering, Software Development, Application Development, Project

Management, Change Management, Requirement Gathering, Agile Methodology, Spring Boot, Apache

Tomcat, Hibernate, Eclipse, iQuery, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Core Java

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

## Summary

Having 2 years of experience as Software Engineer in Java and J2EE technologies.

Excellent hands of experience with Java/J2EE Technologies covering J2SE,JSP, Spring and Hibernate.

Sound Knowledge in Oracle and PostgreSQL.

Having good Analytical, Programming and Problem Solving Skills.

Has the motivation to take independent responsibility as well as ability to contribute and b e a productive team player.

Ability to learn new Technologies and tools quickly.

Capable of adopting to work on new Technologies and Environments easily

## Work Experience

#### BRACKET TECHNOLOGY PRIVATE LIMITED as Java Developer

Jul 2018 to Oct 2020

PROJEECT1: SmartSupplies PMD(Planning Manufacturing and distribution)

Role: Developer

Designation: Java Developer

Team Size: 16 (7 Dev,7 QA, 2 Manager) Client: Shire, Sanofi Aventis, Allergan.

Smart Supplies PMD is easy to use, fully web enabled solution empowers Biotechnology and Pharmaceutical organizations of all sizes to effectively Plan, Monitor and Control the clinical supplies process. Smart Supplies solution provides a protocol driven framework coupled with bi-directional integration to manufacturing systems, IVR services. Smart Supplies is designed to dramatically increase the efficiency, accuracy and compliance of the clinical supply process with immediate benefits including Planning, Manufacturing, Packaging and Distribution, Management and Control. Responsibilities:

Worked on Conversion into HTML5, business logic and Multi level approval functionalities, Solving JIRA Task.

Worked on Branches, Items module.

PROJEECT2: RADAR Role: Developer

Designation: Java Developer

Team Size: 11 (4 Dev,4 QA,1PO,2 Manager) Client :SANOFI.

Description:

\* RADAR is Clinical Trials related Application where clinical trials will going to conduct on volunteers. The application can

hold the data that which patient is assigned by which kit on which visit. After successful clinical Trials that manage the flow of drug back from site through to eventual destruction.

Involved in collecting the requirements from Client.

Interact with Management to understand the requirements and clarifying the doubts.

Worked for the user requirements and prepared the software functional activities.

Coded all the POJO's required for this system.

Involved in designing view pages using Spring MVC.

Involved in coding DAO classes and mapping files using Hibernate.

Also involved in coding of all Logging Activities using Log4J Framework.

Participated daily in Scrum meets to discuss different issues in the project.

Coordinated with co team members to develop high level business and technical Documents.

### Bracket Technology as Java Developer

Jul 2018 to Till Date

- ? Involved in collecting the requirements from Client.
- ? Interact with Management to understand the requirements and clarifying the doubts.
- ? Worked for the user requirements and prepared the software functional activities.
- ? Coded all the POJO?s required for this system.
- ? Involved in designing view pages using Spring MVC.
- ? Involved in coding DAO classes and mapping files using Hibernate.
- ? Also involved in coding of all Logging Activities using Log4J Framework.
- ? Participated daily in Scrum meets to discuss different issues in the project.
- ? Coordinated with co team members to develop high level business and technical Documents.

### **Education**

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Electronics/Telecommunication) from Cmr institute of engineering and technology. in 2016

PG: in 0

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
JAVA	8	2018	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
J2EE		2018	1 Year(s)
SPRING CORE		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
SPRING MVC		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
spring boot		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Hibernate		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
HTML			
css			
JavaScript			
Reactjs			
Oracle			
PostgreSQL		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
Apache Tomcat		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
WebLogic			
MICRO SERVICES		2020	0 Year(s) 6 Month(s)
cvs			
GitHub		2020	6 Month(s)

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient			
Hindi	Beginner			
Telugu	Expert			

## **Projects**

**Project Title: RADAR** Client: SANOFI.

Nature of Employment: Full Time **Duration: May 2020 - Oct 2020 Project Location: Hyderabad** Onsite / Offsite: Offsite

Role: Programmer Team Size: 11 Skill Used: Core Java, Spring Boot, Hibernate, React.Js, Postgresql, Amazon Ec2,

Role Description: \* Involved in collecting the requirements from Client. Interact with Management to understand the

requirements and clarifying the doubts.

Coded all the POJO's required for this system. Involved in designing view pages using Spring MVC.

Project Details: RADAR is Clinical Trials related Application where clinical trials will going to conduct on volunteers. The application can hold the data that which patient is assigned by which kit on which visit. After successful clinical Trials that manage the flow of drug back from site through to eventual destruction.

#### **Affirmative Action**

#### **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent / Temporary

**Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time**